<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">DroidPI</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="action_about">About this application</string>
    <string name="action_return">Return to application</string>
    <string name="action_exit">Exit</string>
    <string name="welcome_text">Welcome to the DroidPI phone benchmarking application!</string>
    <string name="proceed_button">Pick a test</string>
    <string name="pi_tests_option">Digits of PI</string>
    <string name="pitest_description">A simple test which computes a large amount of the digits of PI to test your processor\nTap the button below when you wish to start the test</string>
    <string name="pitest_start_button">Start computing dem\' digits</string>
    <string name="pitest_wait_button">Because 3.14 is too abrupt an end...</string>
    <string name="pitest_wait_text">Computing all the digits of PI and then some</string>
    <string name="pitest_finished_text">Enough digits have been computed to rule the world!</string>
    <string name="threads_tests_option">Threads</string>
    <string name="threadstest_description">A test which assesses your device\'s thread handling capabilities\nTap the button below when you wish to start the test</string>
    <string name="threadstest_start_button">Launch enough threads to rule the world</string>
    <string name="threadstest_wait_button">Threading into oblivion...</string>
    <string name="threadstest_wait_text">Putting the complexity of the universe to shame through multithreading</string>
    <string name="threadstest_finished_text">Almost lost sight of reality there for a sec...</string>
    <string name="arithmetic_tests_option">Arithmetics</string>
    <string name="arithmetictest_description">A test which gauges your device\'s arithmetic capabilities.\nTap the button below when you wish to start the test</string>
    <string name="arithmetictest_start_button">Compute all the things!</string>
    <string name="arithmetictest_wait_button">Putting mathematicians to shame...</string>
    <string name="arithmetictest_wait_text">Please wait while we compute the distance to infinity</string>
    <string name="arithmetictest_finished_text">Crunched so many numbers I now have a 6-pack</string>
    <string name="recursion_tests_option">Recursion</string>
    <string name="recursiontest_description">This test focuses on testing your phone\'s recursion capabilities\nTap the button below when you wish to start the test</string>
    <string name="recursiontest_start_button">S...ss...s..start stuttering</string>
    <string name="recursiontest_wait_button">S....s......sss....s.sss...s</string>
    <string name="recursiontest_wait_text">Please wait while we\'re repeating ourselves</string>
    <string name="recursiontest_finished_text">I hope that stutter ww..wares off eventually</string>
    <string name="title_activity_tests">Pick your test</string>
    <string name="back_to_tests_title">Back to tests</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="back_button">Try another test?</string>
    <string name="title_activity_pitest">Digits of PI Computation Test</string>
    <string name="title_activity_threadstest">Threading capabilities test</string>
    <string name="title_activity_arithmetic_test">Arithmetic Capabilities Test</string>
    <string name="title_activity_recursion_test">Recursion Assessment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about_app">About this Application</string>

    <string name="app_description">This application was developed by Stefania-Bianca Costache and
        Nashwan-Mouhammad Azhari, two students from the University \"Politehnica\" of Timisoara,
        as part of their practical assignment for the subject entitled \"Computer Organization\";
        all under the exquisite guidance of Professor Mircea Udrescu, the course\'s head lecturer, and Professor
        Alexandru Topirceanu, the one in charge of the laboratory hours, for whose respective involvements we are
        thoroughly in debt. \n\nEntitled simply \"DroidPI\", a name derived from the very first benchmark
        we have ever written, this application aims to serve a narrow but significant nieche: that of the
        simple, straightforward and non-invasive benchmarking of Android devices.\nWe focused
        on four major benchmarks, each one designed specifically to test a certain performance aspect
        of your device\'s CPU.\nAlthough, as some may argue, rudimentary, DroidPI offers the quickest approach
        to gauging your phone\'s real world computational capabilities without requiring any sort of permissions
        apart from that of basic running.\n\nThe benchmarked algorithms (the computation of the digits of PI,
        the use of numerous threads for the obtaining of a square root, the incessant recursive calling of
        the same function for finding more and more primes and the repeated execution of a handful of arithmetic
        operations) were all adapted for use in our project by Stefania, whilst the overall design and implementation
        of the application itself was done by Nashwan.\n\nAs far as the scoring system goes:\nAll of the benchmarks
        are run and their respective execution times are measured in an utmost isolative manner, the application then
        offering the results in milliseconds, as well as a per 100 score which relates your result to the scores obtained by
        the Samsung Galaxy S4, arguably one of the most powerful phones on the market upon this application\'s inception.\n
        Now granted, due to numerous outside influences the final assessed score may vary, even exceeding 100 in the case of
        higher end phones. The shortcomings of the scoring system were part of the compromise of making the application as
        transparent and non-invasive as possible whilst still offering a tangible result apart from a time measurement /n/n
        As the authors, we would like to thank you for trying out the application. Although it may seem insignificant
        to you, the making of this greatly contributed to the skillsets and overall awareness of the developers and
        vastly broadened their knowledge of the working of hardware benchmarking, an activity we hope to partake in
        again in the near future.\n\nIf you have (surprisingly) stayed with us this long, and because we are firm
        advocates of the Open-Source model, we would like to welcome you to view, analyse, fork and freely use
        the source code for this application, which can be found in full Android Studio Gradle project form at /n\n
        https://github.com/aznashwan/DroidPI
    </string>

</resources>